Today I am going to try Parathas and
Pakora from Maap Bhai. These people
came in Shark Tank and after listening to their founder's voice,
honestly, I burst out laughing.
Their parathas and pakoras are not 100% delicious
and they remain crispy even after delivery.
I ordered their Aloo Pyaz Pratham by mail
and also ordered Palak
Pakora. Now give me one paratha in the mill. Also give me the gravy,
butter curd,
Jaan Hosli Paratha Naam. From the side, it was
not cooked properly and look, it was a little cooked
but that's enough. The
paratha tastes good and this orange
gravy, it is Shahi Paneer gravy,
10 pieces and Power Pakora and
they also sent green chutney along with it, which
tasted just fine. If seen, it is
not a bad business venture, if I were there, I would
probably invest in it.